Christian Horban

Web Developer

Contact

Summary

Parker, CO 80134 christian.k,horban@gmail.com A web developer with a diverse professional background and experience in technical support roles. Strives to apply their skills in React, Node, Express, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to design innovative and user-friendly experiences, embracing feedback and continuously improving.

Education

CareerFoundry Full-Stack Development

Key Skills

Full-Stack Development
HTML, CSS, JavaScript
React.js, Node.js, jQuery, Redux
MERN Stack
REST API Design
State Routing
Database Architecture
Technical Analysis
Planning and Coordination
Team Leadership
Interpersonal Communication
Complex Problem-solving

Tools

<u>GitHub</u>

Visual Studio Code CodePen Bootstrap jQuery Chrome Developer Tools

Experience

September 2022 - Current

Technical Support • Vertafore

- Investigated and resolved technical issues to ensure the smooth functionality of websites and applications.
- Collaborated with clients to evaluate and recommend solutions for complex challenges.

February 2022 – June 2022

Account Specialist • Coinbase

- Demonstrated expertise in product and industry knowledge and best practices.
- Performed thorough investigations into client accounts security incidents to mitigate risk and identify the source for loss of funds.

June 2021 – February 2022

Application Analyst • Applied Statistics and Management

- Documented client issues and resolutions, maintaining accurate records for future reference and continuous improvement.
- Conducted troubleshooting, maintenance, and optimization of applications to enhance performance and user experience.

September 2017 – December 2019

IT Support Specialist II • The Smart Circle

- Effectively communicated technical information to clients, providing clear and concise guidance and support.
- Conducted thorough assessments of existing processes and identified bottlenecks, inefficiencies, and areas for optimization.

May 2017 - September 2017

Help Desk Analyst • SC Fuels

- Provided basic end-user troubleshooting and desktop support on Windows, Linux, and Mac systems.
- Documented transactions and support interactions in system for future reference and addition to knowledge base.

Portfolio

Click Here!